

PHẠM PHÁI HÀ

OBJECTIVE

DEVELOPER

I'm currently a senior developer. i'm a front-end developer with over 4 years of experience. I has worked in the fields of software development, E-commerce, ERP, CRM and blockchain related projects. I is passionate about technology and cryptocurrency.

LinkCV: https://www.phamha.info/

SỐ ĐIỆN THOẠI

0886323318

EMAIL

phamhande@gmail.com

WEBSITE

ĐỊA CHỈ

Ha Noi

WORK EXPERIENCE

TEKMATE SOFTWARE SOLUTION

12-2019 - 04-2020

ProjectName :Xaydung Co

Member: 10 (2 Tester, 6 Dev, 1 PM, 1

BA)

Position: InternProject Description:

Building web app for selling

construction company's tools like

Fiver.

Technology: React JS, Node(Express)

Work Description: create UI/UX, work

with BE dev and add api

Work Description: make UI/UX like a

design, work with BE dev and add api

GMO-Z.COM RUNSYSTEM

07-2020 - 12-2020

ProjectName :Sale fie

Member: 18 (3 Tester, 8 Dev, 1 PM, 2

BA, 2 QA, 1BO, 1Leader)Position:

ReactJs developerProject Description:

staffs management

project, Technology Award 'Sao Khue

2021' of vietnam. Award Link:

https://runsystem.net/vi/2021/04/26

/gmo-z-com-runsystem-nhan-cu-dup-

2-danh-hieu-sao-khue-2021-cho-san-

pham-chuyen-doi/Technology: React

JS, Node(GraphQl,Express) Work

Description: make UI/UX like a design,

work with BE dev and add api

Link: https://salefie.vn/

GMO-Z.COM RUNSYSTEM

12-2020 - 05-2021

ProjectName:kaike

Member: 13 (3 Tester, 7 Dev, 1 PM, 1

BA,1 QA)

Position: ReactJs developerProject
Description: website accounting
project. Helping users who do not
know about accounting can also do a

EDUCATION

 TRANSPORTATION TECHNOLOGY UNIVERSITY

August - 2017 - 2021

Major:Information Technology

4th year student

VTC ACADEMY

August - 2018 - 2021

Major:Web full-Stack

Graduated

professional accountant

Technology: React JS (webpack),

Node(GraphQl ,Express) Work

Description: make UI/UX like a design,

work with BE dev and add api Link: https://app.kaike.vn/

GMO-Z.COM RUNSYSTEM

05-2021 - 07-2021

ProjectName :Admin PL

Member: 13 (3 Tester, 7 Dev, 1 PM, 1

BA,1 QA)Position: ReactJs

developerProject Description :work

time management

Technology: React JS (webpack),

Node(Express) Work Description:

make UI/UX like a design, work with

BE dev and add api, manage project

front-end

Link: private

GMO-Z.COM RUNSYSTEM

07-2021 - 09-2021

ProjectName: MySGR (onsite)

Member: 14 (3 Tester, 7 Dev, 1 PM, 2

BA,1 QA, 1 Team lead, 1 Tech lead)

Position: ReactJs developer, review

code, tech leadProject Description

:Staffs management off Sun Group

Technology: React JS (webpack),

Node (ODDO) Work Description: make

UI/UX like a design, work with BE dev

and add api, manage project front-

end, work with filebase, backend

ODDO, review code, merge code

Link: private

FILINK

11-2021 - 3-2022

ProjectName: LSTN (product)

Member: (5 front-end)Position:

ReactJs developer, teamleadProject

Description : Auction of NFT products

Technology: React JS ,Web3jsWork

Description: make UI/UX like a design,

work with BE dev and add api, manage project front-end, call data from Blockchain. convert many money, connect metamask wallet
Link: https://listencampaign.com/list en_campaign_elements

FPT

3-2022 - End

ProjectName: Aura-Safe(product)

Member: (1 front-end)Position: ReactJs developer, Project

Description: Look like gnosis safe,

manager many wallet cryto

Technology: React JS ,Web3jsWork
Description: make UI/UX like a design,
work with BE dev and add api,call data
form Blockchain. connect keplr, coin
98 wallet

Link: https://test.pyxis.aura.network/

welcomeLink

landing: https://pyxis.aura.network/

© topcv.vn